{"data":[{"question":"The relationship of Latin American music to Black music in the United States is clearly evident in the unaccented beats that are common to either.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of ","b":"to ","c":"clearly evident ","d":"either","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Either-> each other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Seven of planets rotate in the same direction as their orbital motions, while Venus and Uranus rotate in the opposite direction.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"planets ","b":"as ","c":"while ","d":"opposite direction","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Of planets-> planets","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"A good exercise program helps teach people to avoid the habits that might shorten the lives.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"helps teach ","b":"to avoid ","c":"might ","d":"the ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- The lives-> their lives","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Nobody should be able to find fault in that argument.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"should ","b":"fault ","c":"in ","d":"argument","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Fault->mistake","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Since the early 1990's Luther Burbank bred a spineless variety of cactus that can be eaten as food.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Since ","b":"variety of ","c":"can be eaten ","d":"as food","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Since-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"A drama is a story intended to be presented by actors onto a stage.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A drama ","b":"intended to ","c":"presented ","d":"onto ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Onto-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"The relationship between law to liberty is even more paradoxical than that between law and order.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"between ","b":"even ","c":"that ","d":"and ","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Between-> of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"An opera combines the excitement of drama and spectacle to the power of music.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"An ","b":"excitement ","c":"drama ","d":"to ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To-> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Jekyll island has been one of Georgia's state parks in 1954.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"one ","b":"state ","c":"parks ","d":"in ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- In-> since","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Bells are frequently made from bronze, an alloy of approximately three part copper and one partin.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"made from ","b":"an alloy ","c":"approximately ","d":"part copper ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Part copper-> parts copper","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}